<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Astra</string>
    <string name="LOGOUT">Logout</string>
    <string name="REGISTER_USER">REGISTER NEW USER</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="license_key">License Key</string>
    <string name="already_have_account_sign_in">Already have Account. Sign In</string>

    <string name="error_email_empty">Email cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="error_email_wrong_format">Wrong email format</string>

    <!--validators-->
    <string name="error_password_empty">Password cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="error_password_length">Password should be atleast 8 letters</string>
    <string name="error_confirm_password_empty">Confirm Password cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="error_license_empty">License cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="error_contact_empty">Contact cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="error_aadhar_empty">Aadhar cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="error_pincode_empty">Pincode cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="invalid_contact">Invalid Contact</string>
    <string name="contact_length_should_be_10">Contact length should be 10</string>
    <string name="invalid_aadhar">Invalid Aadhar</string>
    <string name="invalid_pincode">Invalid Pincode</string>
    <string name="dont_have_account_create_one">Dont\' have Account. Create One</string>
    <string name="field_cannot_be_left_blank">Field can\'t be left blank</string>
    <string name="error_dob_empty">Date can\'t be blank</string>
    <string name="invalid_date">Invalid Date Format</string>

    <!--   admin home screen -->
    <string name="admin_home_switch_label_out">OUT</string>
    <string name="press_to_scan_qr_here">QrScanner</string>
    <string name="admin_search_username_label">Enter Username</string>
    <string name="desc_of_send">SendDataButton</string>
    <string name="cd_scanner">TODO</string>
    <string name="click_here_to_scan">Click here to Scan</string>
    <string name="or">OR</string>
    <string name="admin_home_screen_wrong_scan_text">Nothing to scan</string>
    <string name="admin_home_screen_retry_action_text">Retry</string>


    <!--    create general user-->
    <string name="create_general_user_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="create_general_fathers_name">Father Name</string>
    <string name="create_general_user_email_address">Email</string>
    <string name="create_general_user_dob">Date Of Birth (DD-MM-YYYY)</string>
    <string name="create_general_user_contact">Contact (10 digit)</string>
    <string name="create_general_user_address">Address</string>
    <string name="create_general_user_aadhar">Aadhar</string>
    <string name="create_general_user_pin_code">Pincode</string>
    <string name="please_correct_all_the_errors">Please correct all the errors</string>


    <string name="doc">Doc</string>
    <string name="save_user">Save</string>
    <string name="front_doc">Front Doc</string>
    <string name="back_doc">Back Doc</string>
    <string name="username">userName</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="verify">Verify</string>

    <!--    Admin Verify Doc-->
    <string name="registered_doc">Registered Doc</string>
    <string name="admin_verify_doc">User Documents</string>
    <string name="scan_alert_msg">Scanning through ASTRA</string>
    <string name="successfully_signed_up">Successfully Signed Up</string>
    <string name="error_signing_up">Error Signing Up !!</string>
    <string name="signin_up">Signing Up ...</string>
    <string name="continue_to_panel">Continue</string>
    <string name="signing_in">Signing In ...</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>

    <!-- search general user -->
    <string name="search_general_user">SEARCH USER</string>
    <string name="saveqr">Save QR</string>
    <string name="myqr">MyQR</string>
    <string name="copy">Copy</string>
    <string name="RemoveQR">RemoveQR</string>

    <!--    admin view report-->
    <string name="DOWNLOAD_REPORT">Download Report</string>
    <string name="DURATION">Duration</string>
    <string name="ERROR_INVALID_DATE_RANGE">Invalid Date Range !!</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_SELECT_THE_DATES">Please select the dates !!</string>
    <string name="excel_mime_type">application/vnd.openxmlformats-officedocument.spreadsheetml.sheet</string>
    <string name="download_template">astra-</string>
    <string name="download_title">Astra</string>
    <string name="purpose">Purpose</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>

    <string name="CompanyName">Pitavya Private Ltd.</string>
    <string name="eula_agreement">
"\n"  	"End-User License Agreement (&quot;Agreement&quot;)\n"
				"Last updated: 4 JULY, 2020\n"
				"Please read this End-User License Agreement (&quot;Agreement&quot;) carefully before clicking the &quot;I Agree&quot;\n"
				"button, downloading or using ASTRA (&quot;Application&quot;).\n"
				"By clicking the &quot;I Agree&quot; button, downloading or using the Application, you are agreeing to be bound\n"
				"by the terms and conditions of this Agreement.\n"
				"If you do not agree to the terms of this Agreement, do not click on the &quot;I Agree&quot; button and do not\n"
				"download or use the Application.\n" 
				"License\n" 
				"PITAVYA PRIVATE LIMITED grants you a revocable, non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited\n" 
				"license to download, install and use the Application solely for your personal, non-commercial\n" 
				"purposes strictly in accordance with the terms of this Agreement.\n" 
				"Restrictions\n" 
				"You agree not to, and you will not permit others to:\n" 
				"license, sell, rent, lease, assign, distribute, transmit, host, outsource, disclose or otherwise\n" 
				"commercially exploit the Application or make the Application available to any third party.\n" 
				"Modifications to Application\n" 
				"PITAVYA PRIVATE LIMITED reserves the right to modify, suspend or discontinue, temporarily or\n" 
				"permanently, the Application or any service to which it connects, with or without notice and without\n" 
				"liability to you.\n" 
				"\n" 
				"Term and Termination\n" 
				"This Agreement shall remain in effect until terminated by you or PITAVYA PRIVATE LIMITED.\n" 
				"PITAVYA PRIVATE LIMITED may, in its sole discretion, at any time and for any or no reason,\n" 
				"suspend or terminate this Agreement with or without prior notice.\n" 
				"This Agreement will terminate immediately, without prior notice from PITAVYA PRIVATE LIMITED,\n" 
				"in the event that you fail to comply with any provision of this Agreement. You may also terminate\n" 
				"this Agreement by deleting the Application and all copies thereof from your mobile device or from\n" 
				"your desktop.\n" 
				"\n" 
				"Upon termination of this Agreement, you shall cease all use of the Application and delete all copies\n" 
				"of the Application from your mobile device or from your desktop.\n" 
				"Severability\n" 
				"If any provision of this Agreement is held to be unenforceable or invalid, such provision will be\n" 
				"changed and interpreted to accomplish the objectives of such provision to the greatest extent\n" 
				"possible under applicable law and the remaining provisions will continue in full force and effect.\n" 
				"Amendments to this Agreement\n" 
				"PITAVYA PRIVATE LIMITED reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to modify or replace this\n" 
				"Agreement at any time. If a revision is material we will provide at least 30 days&#39; notice prior to any\n" 
				"new terms taking effect. What constitutes a material change will be determined at our sole\n" 
				"discretion.\n" 
				"Contact Information\n" 
				"If you have any questions about this Agreement, please contact us – contact@pitavya.com";


    </string>
    <string name="privacy_policy"> "ASTRA\nLast updated 04 JULY, 2020\n
        <b>PITAVYA PRIVATE LIMITED</b> (“we” or “us” or “our”) respects the privacy of our users (“user” or
				“you”). This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your
				information when you visit our mobile application (the “Application”). Please read this Privacy
				Policy carefully. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY,
				PLEASE DO NOT ACCESS THE APPLICATION.\n"
				"We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. We\n" 
				"will alert you about any changes by updating the “Last updated” date of this Privacy Policy. You\n" 
				"are encouraged to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed of updates. You will\n" 
				"be deemed to have been made aware of, will be subject to, and will be deemed to have\n" 
				"accepted the changes in any revised Privacy Policy by your continued use of the Application\n" 
				"after the date such revised Privacy Policy is posted.\n" 
				"This Privacy Policy does not apply to the third-party online/mobile store from which you install\n" 
				"the Application or make payments, including any in-game virtual items, which may also collect\n" 
				"and use data about you. We are not responsible for any of the data collected by any such third\n" 
				"party.\n" 
				"COLLECTION OF YOUR INFORMATION\n" 
				"We may collect information about you in a variety of ways. The information we may collect via\n" 
				"the Application depends on the content and materials you use, and includes:\n" 
				"Personal Data\n" 
				"Demographic and other personally identifiable information (such as your name and email\n" 
				"address) that you voluntarily give to us when choosing to participate in various activities related\n" 
				"to the Application, such as chat, posting messages in comment sections or in our forums, liking\n" 
				"posts, sending feedback, and responding to surveys. If you choose to share data about yourself\n" 
				"via your profile, online chat, or other interactive areas of the Application, please be advised that\n" 
				"all data you disclose in these areas is public and your data will be accessible to anyone who\n" 
				"accesses the Application.\n" 
				"Derivative Data\n" 
				"Information our servers automatically collect when you access the Application, such as your\n" 
				"native actions that are integral to the Application, including liking, re-blogging, or replying to a\n" 
				"post, as well as other interactions with the Application and other users via server log files.\n" 
				"\n" 
				"Geo-Location Information\n" 
				"\n" 
				"We may request access or permission to and track location-based information from your mobile\n" 
				"device, either continuously or while you are using the Application, to provide location-based\n" 
				"services. If you wish to change our access or permissions, you may do so in your device’s\n" 
				"settings.\n" 
				"Mobile Device Access\n" 
				"We may request access or permission to certain features from your mobile device, including\n" 
				"your mobile device’s [bluetooth, calendar, camera, contacts, social media accounts, storage,]\n" 
				"and other features. If you wish to change our access or permissions, you may do so in your\n" 
				"device’s settings.\n" 
				"Mobile Device Data\n" 
				"Device information such as your mobile device ID number, model, and manufacturer, version of\n" 
				"your operating system, phone number, country, location, and any other data you choose to\n" 
				"provide.\n" 
				"Push Notifications\n" 
				"We may request to send you push notifications regarding your account or the Application. If you\n" 
				"wish to opt-out from receiving these types of communications, you may turn them off in your\n" 
				"device’s settings.\n" 
				"\n" 
				"USE OF YOUR INFORMATION\n" 
				"Having accurate information about you permits us to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and\n" 
				"customized experience. Specifically, we may use information collected about you via the\n" 
				"Application to:\n" 
				"1. Administer sweepstakes, promotions, and contests.\n" 
				"2. Assist law enforcement and respond to subpoena.\n" 
				"3. Compile anonymous statistical data and analysis for use internally or with third parties.\n" 
				"4. Create and manage your account.\n" 
				"5. Deliver targeted advertising, coupons, newsletters, and other information regarding\n" 
				"promotions and the Application to you.\n" 
				"6. Email you regarding your account or order.\n" 
				"7. Enable user-to-user communications.\n" 
				"8. Fulfill and manage purchases, orders, payments, and other transactions related to the\n" 
				"Application.\n" 
				"9. Generate a personal profile about you to make future visits to the Application more\n" 
				"personalized.\n" 
				"10. Increase the efficiency and operation of the Application.\n" 
				"11. Monitor and analyze usage and trends to improve your experience with the Application.\n" 
				"12. Notify you of updates to the Application.\n" 
				"13. Offer new products, services, mobile applications, and/or recommendations to you.\n" 
				"14. Perform other business activities as needed.\n" 
				"\n" 
				"15. Prevent fraudulent transactions, monitor against theft, and protect against criminal\n" 
				"activity.\n" 
				"16. Process payments and refunds.\n" 
				"17. Request feedback and contact you about your use of the Application.\n" 
				"18. Resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems.\n" 
				"19. Respond to product and customer service requests.\n" 
				"20. Send you a newsletter.\n" 
				"21. Solicit support for the Application.\n" 
				"22. [Other]\n" 
				"\n" 
				"DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION\n" 
				"We may share information we have collected about you in certain situations. Your information\n" 
				"may be disclosed as follows:\n" 
				"By Law or to Protect Rights\n" 
				"If we believe the release of information about you is necessary to respond to legal process, to\n" 
				"investigate or remedy potential violations of our policies, or to protect the rights, property, and\n" 
				"safety of others, we may share your information as permitted or required by any applicable law,\n" 
				"rule, or regulation. This includes exchanging information with other entities for fraud protection\n" 
				"and credit risk reduction.\n" 
				"\n" 
				"Online Postings\n" 
				"When you post comments, contributions or other content to the Applications, your posts may be\n" 
				"viewed by all users and may be publicly distributed outside the Application in perpetuity\n" 
				"\n" 
				"Affiliates\n" 
				"We may share your information with our affiliates, in which case we will require those affiliates\n" 
				"to honor this Privacy Policy. Affiliates include our parent company and any subsidiaries, joint\n" 
				"venture partners or other companies that we control or that are under common control with us.\n" 
				"Business Partners\n" 
				"We may share your information with our business partners to offer you certain products,\n" 
				"services or promotions.\n" 
				"\n" 
				"Social Media Contacts\n" 
				"If you connect to the Application through a social network, your contacts on the social network\n" 
				"will see your name, profile photo, and descriptions of your activity.\n" 
				"Sale or Bankruptcy\n" 
				"If we reorganize or sell all or a portion of our assets, undergo a merger, or are acquired by\n" 
				"\n" 
				"another entity, we may transfer your information to the successor entity. If we go out of\n" 
				"business or enter bankruptcy, your information would be an asset transferred or acquired by a\n" 
				"third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and that the transferee may decline\n" 
				"honor commitments we made in this Privacy Policy.\n" 
				"We are not responsible for the actions of third parties with whom you share personal or\n" 
				"sensitive data, and we have no authority to manage or control third-party solicitations. If you no\n" 
				"longer wish to receive correspondence, emails or other communications from third parties, you\n" 
				"are responsible for contacting the third party directly.\n" 
				"TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES\n" 
				"Internet-Based Advertising\n" 
				"Additionally, we may use third-party software to serve ads on the Application, implement email\n" 
				"marketing campaigns, and manage other interactive marketing initiatives. This third-party\n" 
				"software may use cookies or similar tracking technology to help manage and optimize your\n" 
				"online experience with us. For more information about opting-out of interest-based ads, visit the\n" 
				"Network Advertising Initiative Opt-Out Tool or Digital Advertising Alliance Opt-Out Tool.\n" 
				"Network Advertising Initiative Opt-Out Tool\n" 
				"You should be aware that getting a new computer, installing a new browser, upgrading an\n" 
				"existing browser, or erasing or otherwise altering your browser’s cookies files may also clear\n" 
				"certain opt-out cookies, plug-ins, or settings.\n" 
				"\n" 
				"SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION\n" 
				"We use administrative, technical, and physical security measures to help protect your personal\n" 
				"information. While we have taken reasonable steps to secure the personal information you\n" 
				"provide to us, please be aware that despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or\n" 
				"impenetrable, and no method of data transmission can be guaranteed against any interception\n" 
				"or other type of misuse. Any information disclosed online is vulnerable to interception and\n" 
				"misuse by unauthorized parties. Therefore, we cannot guarantee complete security if you\n" 
				"provide personal information.\n" 
				"POLICY FOR CHILDREN\n" 
				"We do not knowingly solicit information from or market to children under the age of 13. If you\n" 
				"become aware of any data we have collected from children under age 13, please contact us\n" 
				"using the contact information provided below.\n" 
				"CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES\n" 
				"Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems [and our mobile applications] include a\n" 
				"Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to\n" 
				"\n" 
				"have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. No uniform technology\n" 
				"standard for recognizing and implementing DNT signals has been finalized. As such, we do not\n" 
				"currently respond to DNT browser signals or any other mechanism that automatically\n" 
				"communicates your choice not to be tracked online. If a standard for online tracking is adopted\n" 
				"that we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that practice in a revised version of\n" 
				"this Privacy Policy.\n" 
				"OPTIONS REGARDING YOUR INFORMATION\n" 
				"[Account Information\n" 
				"You may at any time review or change the information in your account or terminate your\n" 
				"account by:\n" 
				"● Logging into your account settings and updating your account\n" 
				"● Contacting us using the contact information provided below\n" 
				"● [Other]\n" 
				"Upon your request to terminate your account, we will deactivate or delete your account and\n" 
				"information from our active databases. However, some information may be retained in our files\n" 
				"to prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms of\n" 
				"Use and/or comply with legal requirements.]\n" 
				"Emails and Communications\n" 
				"If you no longer wish to receive correspondence, emails, or other communications from us, you\n" 
				"may opt-out by:\n" 
				"● Noting your preferences at the time you register your account with the Application\n" 
				"● Logging into your account settings and updating your preferences.\n" 
				"● Contacting us using the contact information provided below\n" 
				"If you no longer wish to receive correspondence, emails, or other communications from third\n" 
				"parties, you are responsible for contacting the third party directly.\n" 
				"CONTACT US\n" 
				"contact@pitavya.com"  </string>


</resources>
